# **AGUSTIN ESPANA**

# agusespa.github.io /profile

+54 11 2406 0018 agusespa@me.com

Hanstavägen 86 164 55 Stockholm Sweden

#### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

I'm a Full Stack Developer and NLP enthusiast counting 10+ years of experience in the tech industry. My main technical skills are focused towards building secure and robust application back-ends with Spring and SQL databases, and intuitive modern web GUIs with React.

#### **CORE SKILLS**

- Web APIs development with Java and Spring
- Web UI development with React and SCSS
- Data persistence with SQL and Hibernate
- Deployment with **Docker** and **Google Cloud Platform**

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Software Developer and Sysadmin at A-Z Editora Publishing House

August 2011 - November 2019 | Buenos Aires, Argentina

- · Back-end development for Apps and E-commerce
- · Front-end Web development
- Development of enriched ebooks
- System administrator
- Online advertising

# **Tech Service Provider (Freelance)**

November 2006 - July 2011 | Buenos Aires, Argentina

- Building and repairing personal computers and small businesses' systems
- Training for individuals and small businesses

### Software developer at Servicio Ambulatorio UTE

April 2006 - October 2006 | Buenos Aires, Argentina

Feature development and maintenance of a software system to track non-emergency ambulance services

# **FORMAL EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor of Arts (BA), Linguistics**

Universidad de Buenos Aires (UBA), Argentina

March 2019 - December 2021 (3 years, not graduated)

Specialized in Formal Linguistics and Natural Language Processing

### **Bachelor of Arts (BA), Advertising**

Universidad de la Empresa (UADE), Argentina

March 2006 - December 2010 (graduated)

Specialized in Digital Advertising

# **Bachelor of Science (BS), Computer Science**

Universidad Tecnológica Nacional (UTN), Argentina

March 2005 - December 2006 (2 years, not graduated)